RASHMI PAURIYAL

Contact: - 8178400198/9999058771

Email: - rashmi.pauriyal@gmail.com

OBIECTIVE

To work in tandem with a team in a challenging and competitive environment where I could improve my knowledge, capabilities and put them to use for the development of the organization.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Knowledge of Multi-media Animation, Corel Draw, Flash & Graphic-Designs
- Ms-Office, Outlook, Internet Concepts, Ms-Excel Data reporting and analysis

SKILLS

- Form expertise
- Strong communication skills
- First aid / CPR
- Demonstrating exercises
- Leadership
- Group instruction
- Program development
- Yoga poses

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Team controller of managerial experience possessing

I have comprehensive knowledge of program management techniques. Accurate versed in database management. Strong organizational, technical and analytical skills. Skilled Operations Leader, talented at improving team performance through innovative management techniques.

Offers thoughtful, comprehensive and constructive feedback to staff members to promote productivity and company loyalty.

Skilled and certified yoga instructor with the ability to build effective relationships with students of all backgrounds and skill levels. Hardworking, dedicated and supportive with excellent communication and problem-solving abilities. Well-versed in compliance requirements, safety and customer service management. Caring, patient and observant leader with an educational style.

EXPERIENCE

Yoga Instructor| **Online Batches**

- Explain different yoga styles and poses to over 30 yoga students per day.
- Develop safe and effective yoga exercise programs for class members.
- Motivate clients to achieve their personal fitness goals by developing and modifying routines.

Team controller | Sequential Technology International Pvt. Ltd. | Jan 2018 - Feb 2023 |

- Working in a Salesforce application
- Customer handling with the Email support
- Worked as Quality Analyst
- Coordinated closely with quality control regarding products awaiting dispositions.
- Always maintained and enforced a safe and clean working environment.
- Preparing productivity planning and conducting sample audits.
- Established and adjusted work procedures to meet production schedules.
- Supervised production schedules, production quality and on time delivery.
- Diligently maintained safety and quality standards.
- Coached employees in developing and achieving individual performance goals.
- Coordinated preventative maintenance on existing and new production equipment. Completed key projects on time, on budget and with a high level of accuracy.

Business Development | Aldebaran Media Pvt. Ltd. 2017 - 2018 |

- Responsible for Adsales, Digital Strategy & proposing Media Buying solutions to direct
- brands
- Responsible for Campaign level planning, execution, forecasting, reporting
- Manage and scale provided set of advertisers; includes activating pending advertisers
- Managing the delivery of campaign through different teams.
- Continuously identifying delivery bottlenecks and taking corrective actions,
- simultaneously guiding, training & aligning team for achieving the goal & meeting
- Acquisition of Indian & International based clients for Branding and Performance based
- campaigns (CPM/CPC/CPV/CPS/CPI etc).

Legal Consultant 12.2015 - 11.2017 | Omni Globe International |

Joined as "Consultant" in December 2015. Currently, working as a Team Controller for US based law firm, order distribution.

Process and handling a team of 50 Consultants / DPE.

Below are my KRAs:

- Provide accurate and appropriate information in response to customer inquiries/queries.
- Address customer service inquiries in a timely and accurate comportment.
- Maintaining/reviewing daily/weekly/monthly dashboards and reports.
- Taking weekly/bi-weekly/monthly customer's calls.
- Reviewing Weekly/monthly performance reports.
- Sharing feedback and action plan for the team. To review the bottom performers and preparing/executing the performance improvement plan.
- Monitoring the team's performance to ensure quality and productivity efficiency.
- To review daily targets, track and maintaining SLAs.
- To ensure all customer inquires/queries are closed within the set TAT.
- Review and executing overtime after analyzing high inflow with the approval of the Supervisor.
- Preparing and sharing monthly performance reports with the client and internal managements.
- Conducting weekly and monthly meeting with the team members and the supervisors.
- Tracking agent performance for creating growth plan for the team.

CustomerRelationshipExecutive|APSTechnology| 05.2015 - 08.2015

- Collected customer feedback and made process changes to exceed customer satisfaction goals.
- Provided accurate and appropriate information in response to customer inquiries.

INTERNSHIP

Graphic Designer | Ashutosh Homeo | 10.10.2011 - 10.03.2012

- Web designing
- Graphic designing

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION

B.A. | 2015 | Delhi University

Graduate in Bachelor of Arts with English.

Diploma | 2011 | Oxford Institute Diplomain Graphic Designing **12**th | **2010 | Kendriya Vidhyalaya**

Higher secondary in Arts from CBSE Board

Diploma | 2020| Yoga Instructor | Morarji Desai National Institute of Yoga

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name: Mr. Surender

Singh Mother's Name: Mrs. Reema Devi Date of Birth:

28-07-1992

Marital Status: Single

Language Known: Hindi, English & Nepali

Residence: Dwarka, New Delhi

SKILLS

- Good in managing client relationship.
- Have a well-organized way of working.
- Good verbal & written communication skills.
- Positive and optimistic nature
- Comprehensive problem solving abilities

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the information provided above is true and to the best of my knowledge and belief.